<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-01-10T06:03:23-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Astoria Runners</title><subtitle>Astoria Runners is about building community through running. We organize weekly runs, group participation in organized races, and other activities.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Welcome</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/update/2024/06/26/welcome-copy.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome" /><published>2024-06-26T14:49:08-04:00</published><updated>2024-06-26T14:49:08-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/update/2024/06/26/welcome%20copy</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/update/2024/06/26/welcome-copy.html"><![CDATA[<p>Astoria Runners is about building community through a shared love of running. We organize weekly runs, group participation in organized races, and other activities.</p>

<p>Our primary run is a 5k / 3-ish mile run on Wednesday evenings in Astoria Park and along the East River. Our pace is generally around 9:30-10:30 min miles. However, all levels of experience and all paces are welcome. We pause at the halfway point and make sure no one is left behind. 
Our weekend runs are 6-13 miles at a 9:30-10:30 pace, and pace varies based on the runners present. Meeting points throughout long run routes ensure folks can choose their own speed and stay with the group. Walking intervals are frequently employed at long runs. Weekend runs will switch from Saturday to Sunday every three months.</p>

<p>We meet at the benches in front of the restrooms by the Astoria Park Track.</p>

<p>NOTE: While running is fun and rewarding, it is not without risk.  When you agree to attend a run, you are certifying that you are responsible for your own actions, and you release and discharge Astoria Runners of any liability for any injury or bodily harm that may occur.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="update" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Astoria Runners is about building community through a shared love of running. We organize weekly runs, group participation in organized races, and other activities.]]></summary></entry></feed>